{
    "Facil": [{
            "id": 0,
            "question": "que es oro y plata no es",
            "answer": "platano",
            "tipoPregunta": "2",
            "imagen": "sadausdas"
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "que le di ce una pulga aun calvo",
            "answer": "No te agaches que me caigo",
            "tipoPregunta": "2",
            "imagen": "sadausdas"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "que es oro y plata no es",
            "answer": "platano",
            "tipoPregunta": "2",
            "imagen": "sadausdas"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "que le di ce una pulga aun calvo",
            "answer": "hola",
            "tipoPregunta": "1",
            "imagen": "sadausdas"
        }
    ],
    "Normal": [{
            "id": 0,
            "question": "que es oro y plata no es",
            "answer": "platano"
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "que le di ce una pulga aun calvo",
            "answer": "No te agaches que me caigo"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "que es oro y plata no es",
            "answer": "platano"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "que le di ce una pulga aun calvo",
            "answer": "No te agaches que me caigo"
        }
    ],
    "Dificil": [{
            "id": 0,
            "question": "que es oro y plata no es",
            "answer": "platano"
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "que le di ce una pulga aun calvo",
            "answer": "No te agaches que me caigo"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "que es oro y plata no es",
            "answer": "platano"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "que le di ce una pulga aun calvo",
            "answer": "No te agaches que me caigo"
        }
    ]
}